Sir Peter...
Peter-sama...
Piglette...
Piglette...
Our guest has consumed the aphrodisiac, sir.
Ela com certeza consumiu o afrodisíaco.
It's the end of the line for that impudent bastard.
Esse é o fim da linha para aquele maldito!
Once his relationship with the Orc turns physical, his engagement to Luvellia shall crumble to pieces...
Assim que ele e a orc tiverem contato físico, o noivado com Luvellia será anulado!
And I shall do him the honor of slicing his head clean off!
E poderei fazer a cabeça dele ir pelos ares!
Forgive me, Peter-Kun...
Me perdoe, Peter-kun...
The Yakeppachi Warriors Guild is on the verge of financial ruin...
A Guilda de Guerreiros Yakepacchi está à beira da falência...
Please, for our sake... Take one for the team!
Por favor, se sacrifique pela nossa Guilda!
Sir Peter... I-I...
Peter-sama... Eu...
My mind is made up...!
Já estou preparada!
Boobs!
Peitos!
The chance to be a hero is long gone...
A chance de ser um herói já era...
Dug myself into a hole with no way out
Mergulhei em um buraco sem saída
Back against the wall... I mean, how could I resist?
Estou contra a parede... quero dizer, como eu poderia resistir?
"This wasn't supposed to happen," I keep denying
"Isso não deveria acontecer", continuo negando
I wish I could just disappear... I can't stand myself
Queria apenas desaparecer... eu não suporto
Moping around, spouting lies, grieving a broken heart
Andando de um lado pro outro, espalhando mentiras, sofrendo por coração partido
I hold on desperately to these feelings and shut my eyes
Me agarro desesperado a esses sentimentos e fecho os olhos
So why does this stupid guilt refuse to go away?!
Mas o remorso se recusa a desaparecer!
I suffocate under its weight
Sou sufocado sob esse peso
The chance to be a hero is long gone...
A chance de ser um herói já era....
Always discouraged by my weaknesses,
Sempre sou desencorajado por minhas fraquezas
I drop to my knees and grovel at your feet,
Caio de joelhos e rastejo aos seus pés
clinging selfishly to the hope for forgiveness
Me apegando de forma egoísta à esperança pelo perdão
Dug myself into a hole with no way out...
Mergulhei em um buraco sem saída
Full of regret and powerless to change,
Cheio de arrependimento e impotente para mudar
I feel my heart being torn apart
Sinto meu coração sendo despedaçado
on this night of endless shame and despair
Nesta noite de vergonha e desespero sem fim
Why can't I get my act together?
Por que não consigo agir direito?
Got nothing but this pathetic self of mine...
Tenho apenas esse meu eu patético...
Boobs!
Peitos!
Peter-kun!
Peter-kun!
Focus!
Não!
W-Wait a minute!
E-Espere!
Episode 6: Peter Grill and the Orc's True Character
Episódio 6 Peter Grill e a verdadeira personalidade da orc
Don't do anything rash...
Não faça nada precipitado!
Besides, weren't you against this whole marriage proposal thing?!
Sei que você também não quer este relacionamento!
No!
Não!
You are mistaken, Sir Peter!
Você está errado, Peter-sama!
If it means being with a noble man like you...
Se for com um homem nobre como você...
Not again!
Não posso!
Don't let her pull you in...!
Se eu me deixar levar...
Listen to me, Piglette!
Me ouça, Piglette!
The truth is...
Na verdade...
I'm already engaged to another woman!
Eu já tenho uma noiva!
So, y'see... it wouldn't be right for us to...
É por isso que não podemos...
Th-That's fine with me...
N-Não me importo...
Sir Peter!
Peter-sama!
Orc relationships are different from Human relationships.
O relacionamento dos orcs é diferente do humano.
Polygyny is the norm!
Somos polígamos!
Not good...!
Não pode!
Take it easy, Piglette!
Piglette, acalme-se!
This entire thing is a setup!
Isto é uma armadilha!
A conspiracy between Orcland and the Guild...
Uma trama entre a Orcland e a Guilda...
They're trying to lure us into a trap!
Tentam nos jogar em uma armadilha!
I-I'm glad you understand...
F-Fico feliz que tenha entendido.
I knew it...
Eu sabia...
I'm not good enough, am I?
Eu não sou boa o bastante, não é?
I'm far too ugly...
Porque sou tão feia...
That's why...!
É por isso que...
N-No!
N-Não!
That's not true!
Isso não é verdade!
You're the furthest thing from ugly!
Você está longe de ser feia!
In my opinion, from a Human perspective...
Na minha opinião, pela perspectiva de um humano...
You're beautiful exactly the way you are!
Você é bela, do jeito que é!
Sir Peter...
Peter-sama...
This is bad...
Isto é péssimo...
Giving in is exactly what the Guildmaster wants...
Se eu cair na tentação, vai ser exatamente o que o Mestre da Guilda quer.
At this point, I can't afford to do any more damage!
Não posso aumentar ainda mais o número de erros!
Then again, I...
Apesar disso, eu...
Absolutely not!
Absolutamente não!
I won't be swayed by an Orc!
Não vou ser enganado por um orc!
Good.
Ótimo!
Just take a deep breath!
Primeiro, devo respirar fundo.
Tap into the Eastern art of "Zen" and clear your mind...
Exploro a arte oriental do "Zen", limpo a mente e...
Remain calm...
Acalme-se...
R-R-R-Remain calm...
Preciso manter a mente clara...
R-R-R-R-R-Re...
E-E-E-E-E-Eu...
BOOBS!
Peitos!!
Why...
Por quê?
Why?!
Por quê?!
Why am I like this?!
Por que sou assim?
Defeated by a pair of boobs...!
Vencido por um par de peitos!
Oh crap...
Essa não...
I'm screwed...
Isto não é nada bom.
Everything up 'til now doesn't even come close...
É pior do que tudo que aconteceu até agora!
If Piglette reports back with the truth about what happened...
Se a Piglette der o relatório de tudo que aconteceu...
How dare you betray the trust of my darling Luvellia...?!
Maldito, você traiu a confiança da minha Luvellia!
He's gonna kill me for sure!
Certamente ele vai me matar!
Anyone with eyes could see that it was a trap...
Qualquer um podia ver que era uma armadilha...
What's WRONG with me?!
O que há de errado comigo?!
What's done is done...
Já que é assim...
There's only one choice left:
Não me resta escolha...
Convince Piglette to keep quiet!
Preciso convencer a Piglette a manter silêncio!
Good morning, Sir Peter.
Bom dia, Peter-sama.
Last night was wonderful, don't you think?
A noite passada foi maravilhosa, não achou?
And now I can deliver the good news to Master Babe:
E agora posso entregar as boas novas ao Babe-sama,
Sir Peter and I have successfully consummated our relationship.
que eu e você tivemos sucesso em atar nosso relacionamento.
H-H-H... H-Hold on!
E-E-Espere um pouco!
You can't tell anyone about this!
Não pode contar nada disto para ele!
What?!
Quê?!
B-But...
M-Mas...
Why not, Sir Peter?!
Por que, Peter-sama?!
Y-Y'see...
É-É que...
Think fast, Peter Grill!
Pense rápido, Peter Grill!
By all accounts, there's no way outta this, BUT...
Não consigo enxergar uma saída, mas...
"When you give up, that's when the game is over!"
Se eu desistir, é fim de jogo!
S-Sir Peter...?
P-Peter-sama?
Are you...
Você...
Are you content with living the rest of your life like a puppet on a string?!
Você aceita continuar a ser um fantoche pelo resto da vida?!
The motive behind this marriage proposal was political from the beginning.
O motivo desta proposta de casamento é político, desde o começo.
One of the most important decisions of your life is being controlled by the national interest!
Uma das decisões mais importantes de sua vida será controlada por interesses de seu país!
Are you truly satisfied with that?!
Vai mesmo aceitar isso?
W-Well, I...
I-Isso eu...
What do you really want?!
O que você realmente quer?
Deep inside your heart, what is it you desire?!
Qual é o desejo que está no fundo do seu coração?
Don't you think you oughtta stop and take the time to consider your options?!
Não acha que deve parar e considerar suas opções?
Well, you can't say I didn't try... Question is, did she buy it...?
Eu tentei, mas será que foi forçado demais?
What I really want...
O que eu quero...
What I desire, deep inside my heart...
O que desejo, do fundo do coração...
L-Let me think it over...
V-Vou pensar um pouco.
Let's hear it, you two!
Muito bem, vocês dois.
How did things go last night?
Como passaram a noite?
Our hope, of course, is that you were able to establish the foundation for a positive relationship.
Nossa esperança, claro, é que foram capazes de estabelecer uma boa relação.
Lady Piglette...
Senhorita Piglette...
Were there any interesting developments after dinner last night?
Tiveram avanços depois do jantar de ontem?
H-Help me out... Please!
P-Por favor, eu peço... Peço por um milagre!
A miracle... Gimme a miracle, just this once!
Preciso que um milagre aconteça!
L-Last night...
N-Na noite passada...
Sir Peter stood firm.
A decisão de Peter-sama foi firme,
He didn't lay a single finger on me!
ele não encostou um dedo em mim!
C-Come again?!
O-O quê?!
Are you telling me this bastard managed to resist the Orc's ample assets?!
Não pode estar dizendo que o maldito conseguiu resistir aos dotes da orc!
It's a miracle...
É um milagre...
My prayers have been answered!
Um milagre aconteceu!
However...
No entanto...
Th-There is one small favor I'd like to ask...
H-Há um favor que eu gostaria de pedir.
P-Piglette...?
P-Piglette?
A-Although the events of last night did not result in physical intimacy...
Apesar dos eventos de ontem não resultarem em contato físico...
I felt an undeniable connection.
S-Senti que tivemos uma conexão!
Therefore, in the name of cultivating a better relationship with Sir Peter from here on out...
Portanto, para cultivar um relacionamento mais profundo com o Peter-sama no futuro...
Stop! Don't do it!
Pare! Não faça isso!
I'd like to request your permission...
Peço a permissão para que eu...
...to transfer to the Guild so as to remain by Sir Peter's side and attend to his needs!
...seja transferida para a Guilda e me manter ao lado do Peter-sama, para servi-lo!
A-ARE YOU SERIOUS?!
O-O que acaba de dizer?!
Rest assured, I shall go to great lengths in order to gain his favor!
Tenho a determinação para conseguir fazer com que ele goste de mim!
All for the sake of our great Orcland's future!
Tudo pelo futuro da Orcland!
Piglette...
Piglette...
What's gotten into you...?!
O que pretende com isso?
Ever since our talk, I've been doing some thinking.
Desde nossa conversa, estive pensando.
About what I really want...
Sobre o que eu realmente quero fazer.
About the desires buried deep within my heart...
Sobre o que eu desejo, do fundo do coração.
I came to a conclusion:
E cheguei a uma decisão.
I shall do everything in my power to prevent Orcland from acquiring your sperm!
Farei de tudo para evitar que a Orcland consiga seu esperma!
Huh?
Hã?
Once you and I have conceived a child who possesses your unrivaled strength...
Terei a criança que vai herdar seu poder inigualável...
I shall raise them, train them...
Vou criá-la, e tendo esse poder...
And harness their power to crush those Orcland pigs who made my life a living hell!
O usarei para esmagar os porcos da Orcland que fizeram da minha vida um inferno!
She's got more issues than I originally thought...
As trevas dentro dela são maiores que pensei.
Something tells me I might've created a monster, one with a terrifying dark side...
Algo me diz que acabei criando um monstro com um terrível lado maligno!
And if nothing else, it means I get to stay by your side forever!
Seja como for, com isso posso ficar ao seu lado, Peter-sama.
I promise to do my best to carry your child, Sir Peter!
Prometo fazer o melhor possível para ter seu filho, Peter-sama.
I may not seem like much of an Orc...
Afinal, sou da raça dos orcs...
But my reproductive abilities are on par with the best of them!
Somos os melhores na habilidade reprodutiva!
Let's enjoy each other's company, Sir Peter!
Espero que nos demos muito bem, Peter-sama!
It started out as a simple crush
No começo era apenas uma paixão
Suddenly, you were my biggest source of strength
De repente, isso se tornou uma grande fonte de força
Till death do us part, let's grow old together
Até que a morte nos separe, vamos envelhecer juntos
This is my sincerest wish:
Este é meu desejo sincero:
Stay with me, stay with me
Fique comigo, fique comigo
So long time, by my side for all eternity
Por tanto tempo, ao meu lado pela eternidade
Beaten down by our daily struggles
Mesmo exausto pelas lutas diárias
Or soaked by a storm of rage;
Ou ensopado por uma tempestade de ira
If you get drenched, I won't hesitate
Se ficar encharcado, não hesitarei
To be the umbrella that shields you
Em ser o guarda-chuvas para te proteger
It's not so cold... I'm by your side
Não é tão frio, se está ao meu lado
That's good enough for me
E isso é o bastante
You're my rock, my strength
Você é o meu porto seguro
That smile of yours puts my soul at ease
Seu sorriso cura minha alma
I could search the whole world over
Mesmo que eu procure ao redor do mundo
And find no one like you
Não há quem te substitua
You're my rock, my strength
Você é meu porto seguro
Just the sight of you fills my heart with joy
Basta sua presença e meu coração se enche de alegria
No matter how much it may hurt,
Não importa o quanto eu me magoe
I pledge my life to protecting you
Ofereço minha vida para te proteger
Dear Sir Peter Grill,
Querido Peter Grill.
Does your roommate Tim still like throwin' back the drinks?
O seu colega de quarto, o Tim-san, ainda adora beber?
Man, I'd love to party with you guys sometime!
Queria que nos juntássemos todos um dia para beber!
Episode 7: Peter Grill and the Battle of the Fates
Episódio 7: Peter Grill e a batalha de destinos